Guide to the Kent State Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1968-1982; Accession 1989-M-048
  - Legal
    - Krause et al. v. Rhodes et al. (Box 4)
      - Post-settlement appeals
        - General, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 220 - 223)
        - Protective order appeal, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 224)
        - Attorney's fees [Sindell] appeal
          - Affidavits, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 225 - 226)
          - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 227)
          - Pleadings, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 228 - 231)
          - Joint appendix, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 232 - 234)
          - Decision, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 235)
    - Krause v. Ohio [Notes, briefs, opinions, miscellanea], 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 236 - 247)
    - Section 1983 cases, 1970-1971, undated (Box 23, Folder 248)
    - Kahler v. Rhodes, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 249 - 250)
    - Krause v. Rhodes; Miller v. Rhodes; Scheuer v. Rhodes [notes, briefs, opinions, miscellanea], 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 251 - 257)
    - Krause v. Rhodes; Miller v. Rhodes [briefs and petitions], 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 258 - 261)
    - Scheuer v. Rhodes (Box 23)
      - General, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 262 - 264)
      - American Civil Liberties Union pleadings, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 265 - 266)
    - Kahler v. Ohio, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 267)
    - Miller v. Ohio, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 268)
    - Krause v. Fassinger, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 269)
    - Schroeder v. Bork, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 270)
    - Schroeder v. Richardson, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 271)
    - Schroeder v. Rhodes, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 272)
    - Schroeder v. Saxbe, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 273)
    - Schroeder v. Kleindienst, 1971-1974, undated (Box 24, Folder 274 - 282)
    - Schroeder v. Kleindienst; Schroeder v. Richardson, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 283)
    - Morgan v. Rhodes, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 284)
    - Gilligan v. Morgan, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 285 - 286)
    - Federal actions against Ohio (unfiled), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 287)
    - Perkins v. Kleindienst, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 288)
    - Palmer v. Hall et al., 1974 (Box 25, Folder 289)
    - Pryor v. Davies, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 290)
    - Saxbe nomination for attorney general (Box 25)
      - Background, 1969-1973 (Box 25, Folder 291 - 292)
      - Background [military law], 1971-1973, undated (Box 25, Folder 293)
      - Litigation, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 294)
      - Testimonies, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - U.S. v. Shafer et al., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 296)
    - CBS v. Young, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 297 - 298)
    - Canfora v. Olds, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 299)
    - Krause v. Jackson, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 300 - 301)
    - Rhodes v. Krause, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 302)
    - Krause et al. v. Ambler et al. [Briefs, memos, correspondence], 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 303 - 306)
    - State of Ohio v. Abdullah, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 307)
    - City of Columbus v. Twohig, Undated (Box 27, Folder 308)
    - Democratic National Committee v. McCord, Undated (Box 27, Folder 309)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War v. Fyke, Undated (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - Background Materials
    - Biographical (Box 27)
      - Berger, Beverley Knowles; Jacobs, Sharon (Malek), 1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 311)
      - Brill, Charles, 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 312)
      - Canterbury, Robert, 1966-1974, undated (Box 28, Folder 313)
      - Delaney, Michael, 1969-1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 314)
      - Del Corso, Sylvester T., 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 315)
      - Denton, Bill, Undated (Box 28, Folder 316)
      - Farriss, James, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 317)
      - Fassinger, Charles S., Undated (Box 28, Folder 318)
      - Filo, John, Undated (Box 28, Folder 319)
      - Haas, Frank, 1973-1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 320)
      - Jones, Harry P., 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 321)
      - Leonard, Jerris, 1970-1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 322)
      - Lutey, Richard, 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 323)
      - McElroy, John M., 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 324)
      - McManus, Matthew, 1974, undated (Box 28, Folder 325)
      - McNeal, Thomas C., 1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 326)
      - McNees, Ronald, 1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 327)
      - Mardian, Robert C., 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 328)
      - Martin, John E., 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 329)
      - Maxwell, Robert, 1975, undated (Box 28, Folder 330)
      - Morris, Barry, Undated (Box 28, Folder 331)
      - Perkins, William S., 1975 (Box 28, Folder 332)
      - Pryor, Myron C. [Mike?], 1970-1975 (Box 28, Folder 333 - 334)
      - Rhodes, James A., 1968-1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 335)
      - Rice, Harold [contains notes and photographs], 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 336)
      - Roese, Donald, Undated (Box 28, Folder 337)
      - Ruffner, Howard, undated (Box 28, Folder 338)
      - Schafer, undated (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - Simons, John W., 1970-1975, undated (Box 29, Folder 340)
      - Snyder, Richard, undated (Box 29, Folder 341)
      - Srp, Raymond, 1970-1974, undated (Box 29, Folder 342)
      - Steigemeier, Rae, undated (Box 29, Folder 343)
      - Strubbs, Terry, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 344)
      - Thomas, Charles, 1971-1978 (Box 29, Folder 345)
      - Tople, Paul, undated (Box 29, Folder 346)
      - York, Florence, 1970-1975, undated (Box 29, Folder 347)
    - Notes (Box 29)
      - General, 1970-1975, undated (Box 29, Folder 348 - 351)
      - Chronology and Petition, undated (Box 29, Folder 352)
      - Defense photos, undated (Box 29, Folder 353)
      - Kent State Memorial panel discussion, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 354)
      - Keysort cards [Kent Cases], undated (Box 29, Folder 355)
      - Movies, undated (Box 29, Folder 356)
      - Tape recording, undated (Box 29, Folder 357)
      - Theories of case, undated (Box 29, Folder 358)
    - Reports (Box 29)
      - After Action Reports, State of Ohio, Adjutant General, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 359)
      - "Analysis of Photographic Evidence and Acoustic Data Pertaining to the Kent State Incident," Electromagnetic Systems Laboratories, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 360)
      - "Analysis of Recorded Sounds from the 1970 Shooting Episode at Kent State University," Bolt, Beranek, and Newman Inc., 1974 (Box 29, Folder 361)
      - "Confidential Report on Interview of Kent State Jurors", undated (Box 29, Folder 362)
      - Investigation report, Bureau of Criminal Investigation, 1970, undated (Box 30, Folder 363)
      - Bureau of Criminal Investigation, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 364)
      - Charts of Movements, Bureau of Criminal Investigation, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 365)
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 366)
      - Efforts to use Freedom of Information Act to obtain Federal Bureau of Investigation reports, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 367)
      - Justice Department summary of Federal Bureau of Investigation reports, 1970, undated (Box 30, Folder 368)
      - Meyer Commission report, Circa 1970 (Box 30, Folder 369 - 371)
      - Bureau Statistics on Use in Domestic Emergencies, National Guard, Circa 1975 (Box 30, Folder 372)
      - Report of the Inspector General, State of Ohio, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 373)
    - Topical (Box 30)
      - Action files, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 374)
      - Address lists, 1978, undated (Box 31, Folder 375)
      - Affirmative defenses, Circa 1975 (Box 31, Folder 376)
      - Assembly, undated (Box 31, Folder 377)
      - Astrological Report for Kent, Ohio, May 4, 1970, 12:30 PM, undated (Box 31, Folder 378)
      - Ballistics, 1970-1975 (Box 31, Folder 379)
      - Case opinions, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 380)
      - Causation and conspiracy, 1974-1975, undated (Box 31, Folder 381)
      - Community attitudes for jury selection, undated (Box 31, Folder 382)
      - Consolidation of lead counsel, [1975?] (Box 31, Folder 383)
      - Court rules, 1973, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 384)
      - Culpability of Rhodes, Del Corso, Canterbury, 1973, undated (Box 31, Folder 385)
      - Depositions, undated (Box 31, Folder 386)
      - Discovery
        - Documentary, 1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 387)
        - Grand jury materials, 1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 388)
      - Documents released by Nixon agent, 1970-1978 (Box 31, Folder 389)
      - Engdahl interview transcript, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 390)
      - Entries of appearance; address changes, 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 391)
      - Federal rules of evidence, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 392)
      - Filmways TV production script, undated (Box 31, Folder 393)
      - Freedom of Information Act, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 394 - 395)
      - Grand juries, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 396)
      - Governor's proclamation, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 397)
      - Index to Kent transcripts; map of jury room, undated (Box 32, Folder 398)
      - Judiciary Committee hearings, 1971-1972, undated (Box 32, Folder 399)
      - Jury Trial under Section 1983, [1975?] (Box 32, Folder 400)
      - Justice Department
        - Memos, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 401)
        - Press conferences, news releases, correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 32, Folder 402)
      - Kent State Archives, undated (Box 32, Folder 403)
      - Kent State Chronology, undated (Box 32, Folder 404)
      - "Kent State," [NBC docudrama], 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 405)
      - Kent State Gymnasium, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 406 - 410)
      - Maps
        - Photographer perspective views, undated (Box 33, Folder 411)
        - Kent State, undated (Box 33, Folder 412)
      - Martial law memoranda, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 413)
      - May 4 memorial activities, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 414)
      - Meeting before press conference, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 415)
      - Memoranda, 1970-1975, undated (Box 33, Folder 416)
      - Memoranda, Office of the President, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 417)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969-1974, undated (Box 33, Folder 418 - 419)
      - Motions to compel; answers to depositions, undated (Box 33, Folder 420)
      - Newsletter, KSU archives, undated (Box 33, Folder 421)
      - Ohio statutes, 1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 422)
      - Operation Plan, State of Ohio Adjutant General, 1970, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 423 - 424)
      - Oral History Collection [Harold Kitner], 1975 (Box 34, Folder 425)
      - Payment of attorney's fees, 1972-1974, undated (Box 34, Folder 426)
      - Petitions
        - Student, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 427)
        - White House [Paul Keene], 1973 (Box 34, Folder 428)
      - Proclamation of Civil Emergency, 1968-1970 (Box 34, Folder 429)
      - Rhodes Press Conference, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 430)
      - Rules of Engagement, 1968-1974 (Box 34, Folder 431)
      - Scranton Commission files, 1970-1975 (Box 34, Folder 432)
      - Self incrimination, 1972, undated (Box 34, Folder 433 - 434)
      - Section 1983, U.S. Code, [1975?] (Box 34, Folder 435)
      - Stay of Proceedings, [1975?] (Box 34, Folder 436)
      - Voir Dire, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 437)
      - Witnesses, undated (Box 34, Folder 438)
      - Witness personal statements, 1970, undated (Box 34, Folder 439)
    - Witness Testimony Index (Box 34)
      - Bambeck, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 440)
      - Berris, Ellis, undated (Box 35, Folder 441)
      - Biddle, Rodney, undated (Box 35, Folder 442)
      - Bishop, Jay, undated (Box 35, Folder 443)
      - Brill, Charles, undated (Box 35, Folder 444)
      - Canfora, Alan, 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 445)
      - Canterbury, Robert, undated (Box 35, Folder 446)
      - Cleary, John, 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 447)
      - Cline, Dwight G., 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 448)
      - Darnell, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 449)
      - Deegan, Charles, undated (Box 35, Folder 450)
      - Delaney, Michael, undated (Box 35, Folder 451)
      - Del Corso, Sylvester, 1970-1975 (Box 35, Folder 452)
      - Denton, Deborah, undated (Box 35, Folder 453)
      - Denton, William, undated (Box 35, Folder 454)
      - Dyal, Robert A., undated (Box 35, Folder 455)
      - Fallon, Howard Richard, undated (Box 35, Folder 456)
      - Farris, James, undated (Box 35, Folder 457)
      - Filo, John, undated (Box 35, Folder 458)
      - Flesher, Okey, undated (Box 35, Folder 459)
      - Grace, Tom, 1974-1975, undated (Box 35, Folder 460)
      - Hatfield, Robert, undated (Box 35, Folder 461)
      - Herschler, William, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 462)
      - Jacobs, Sharon, undated (Box 36, Folder 463)
      - James, Robert, 1970-1975, undated (Box 36, Folder 464)
      - Jones, Harry, undated (Box 36, Folder 465)
      - Kahler, Dean, undated (Box 36, Folder 466)
      - Kamber, Gerald, undated (Box 36, Folder 467)
      - Lewis, Joseph, undated (Box 36, Folder 468)
      - Locher, Paul, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 469)
      - Love, Richard, 1970-1975, undated (Box 36, Folder 470)
      - Mackenzie, Donald Scott, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 471)
      - McGee, James D., undated (Box 36, Folder 472)
      - McManus, Matthew J., 1970-1975 (Box 36, Folder 473)
      - McNees, Ronald, undated (Box 36, Folder 474)
      - Martin, John, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 475)
      - Montgomery, Harry, undated (Box 36, Folder 476)
      - Montgomery, William, undated (Box 36, Folder 477)
      - Morris, Barry W., undated (Box 36, Folder 478)
      - Mowrer, Larry R., 1970-1975, undated (Box 36, Folder 479)
      - Perkins, William, undated (Box 36, Folder 480)
      - Pickett, Robert, undated (Box 36, Folder 481)
      - Pierce, James B., 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 482)
      - Pryor, Myron C., 1970-1974, undated (Box 37, Folder 483)
      - Rhodes, James, 1974, undated (Box 37, Folder 484)
      - Ruffner, Howard, undated (Box 37, Folder 485)
      - Russell, James, 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 486)
      - Shafer, Lawrence, 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 487)
      - Smith, Leon, undated (Box 37, Folder 488)
      - Snyder, James Ronald, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 489)
      - Stamps, Robert, 1970-1975 (Box 37, Folder 490)
      - Stevenson, Alexander D., 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 491)
      - Stiegemeier, Rae, undated (Box 37, Folder 492)
      - Thomas, Lloyd W., undated (Box 37, Folder 493)
      - Wrentmore, Douglas, 1970-1975, undated (Box 37, Folder 494)
      - Zoller, Ralph W., 1970, undated (Box 37, Folder 495)
    - Writings (Box 37)
      - Davies, Peter, "An Appeal for Justice", 1971 (Box 38, Folder 496 - 497)
      - Engdahl, David
        - "The Military Takeover", 1974 (Box 38, Folder 498)
        - "Nix-on Justice", 1972 (Box 38, Folder 499)
        - Saxbe nomination, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 500)
        - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 501)
  - General Correspondence
    - General [among counsel], 1970-1975 (Box 39, Folder 502)
    - General, 1973-1979 (Box 39, Folder 503)
    - Adams, John [Board of Christian Social Concerns], 1971-1978 (Box 39, Folder 504)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 505)
    - Applications for funding, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 506)
    - Board of Church and State, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 507)
    - Canfora, Alan, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 508)
    - Clark, Ramsey, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 509)
    - "Crank letters", 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 510)
    - Davies, Peter, 1971-1980 (Box 39, Folder 511)
    - Davies, Peter; Gordon, Bill; Edwards Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 512)
    - Fisher, Dorothy, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 513)
    - Gerner, Henry [Ohio Council of Churches], 1972, undated (Box 39, Folder 514)
    - Gordon, Bill, 1972-1980 (Box 40, Folder 515 - 518)
    - Henderson, Ron [American Report], 1972 (Box 40, Folder 519)
    - Hensley, Thomas, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 520)
    - Keane, Paul, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 521)
    - Keller, Steven, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 522)
    - Krause, Arthur, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 523)
    - Kuhn, David, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 524)
    - May 4 Taskforce, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 525)
    - Michener, James, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 526)
    - Morse, Louis James, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 527)
    - National Council of Churches, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 528)
    - Photographs, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 529)
    - Playboy Forum, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 530)
    - Protest groups, 1972, undated (Box 40, Folder 531)
    - Published writings (Box 40)
      - General, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 532)
      - Military troops in civil disturbances, 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 533)
    - Rosen, Sanford, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 534)
    - Saxbe nomination, 1971-1973 (Box 41, Folder 535)
    - Schollenberger, Charles, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 536)
    - Sindell, Steven, 1970-1974 (Box 41, Folder 537)
    - White House, Attorney General, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 538)
    - Yale University Archives, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 539)
    - Young, Don J., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 540)
    - Young, Senator Stephen, 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 541)
  - Clippings
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1980 (Box 42, Folder 542 - 550)
    - Crewdson, John M., 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 551)
    - Editorials, cartoons, commentary, 1971-1978 (Box 43, Folder 552 - 553)
    - Marked copies, major news articles with witnesses, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 554)
    - May 4 Memorial Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 555)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 556)
    - "With useful factual information, evidence", 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 557)
    - "No useful factual information", 1970-1974 (Box 43, Folder 558 - 559)
    - Photography and journalism as court evidence, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 560)
    - Posters, 1973-1980 (Box 43, Folder 561)
    - Press releases, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 562)
    - Rhodes testimony, 1974 July (Box 43, Folder 563)
    - Saxbe nomination`, 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 564)
    - Miscellaneous books, newspapers, videotape, 1970-1983 (Box 44)
  - Photographs
    - Aerial views of Kent State campus, undated (Box 45, Folder 565)
    - Contact sheets (Box 45)
      - General, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 566)
      - Cleary, John R., 1970 (Box 45, Folder 567)
      - Plaintiffs' exhibit, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 568)
      - Scoobie, Harold, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 569)
    - Slides [Greg Moore], undated (Box 45, Folder 570)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 45, Folder 571 - 578)
    - Negatives (Box 45)
      - 4x5, mostly black and white, Circa 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        Many of these photographs contain Plaintiff's Exhibit labels with numbers, and several are identified as being taken by Howard E. Ruffner.
      - 4x5, color, of the bodies of the four students killed at Kent State, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, 4x5, black and white, some color, Circa 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Includes images and proof sheets by the following photographers: Marcia L. Adams, Richard Boeme, Lloyd D. Heilman, Lori Legge, Gregory Moore, Terrance B. Norman, Timothy Oleski, James Peck, Harold Scoobie, Victor Sloan, Patricia Sorse, and Terry Wilson.
    - Color transparencies, 35 mm, of P1 injuries, Circa 1970 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Slides documenting the site of the Kent State shootings, Circa 1970-1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, 35 mm, black and white, of mounted photographs of events at Kent State University on 4 May 1970, Circa 1970-1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, 8 mm, black and white, of Kent State scenes, including what appear to be bullet holes in buildings, Circa 1970 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Notes, undated (Box 49, Folder 579 - 582)
    - Prints (Box 49)
      - Duplicates, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 583)
      - Duplicates [Eads], 1970 (Box 49, Folder 584)
      - Duplicates and letter [Patricia Scorce], 1970-1975 (Box 49, Folder 585)
      - Ling movie frames [Kahlher running and falling], 1970 (Box 49, Folder 586)
      - [Group snapshot of plaintiffs and counsel?], [1979?] (Box 49, Folder 587)
      - Plaintiffs' exhibit book, undated (Box 49, Folder 588 - 589)
      - Reprints [8x10]
        - Miscellaneous for second trial, undated (Box 50, Folder 590 - 593)
        - Miscellaneous, 1970, undated (Box 50, Folder 594 - 599)
      - Reprints [organized sequentially], 1970 (Box 51)
      - Reprints [organized sequentially], 1970 (Box 52)
    - Oversized contact sheets and negatives, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 600)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Exhibit 50022 (Lord tape) [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 54)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 54D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 54U)
    - Exhibit 50022 [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 55)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 55D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 55U)
    - Exhibit 50023, "before shots" [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 56)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 56D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 56U)
    - Exhibit 50023 and 50024, "shots and after shots" [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 57)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 57D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 57U)
    - Exhibit 50024, "last 10 minutes" [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 58)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 58D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 58U)
    - Strubbe tape [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 59)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 59D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 59Ua)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 59Ub)
    - Peter Davies' phone call (White House involvement) [restricted], circa 1970s (Box 60)
      - Duplicating master, 1 (Box 60D)
      - Use copy, audiocassette (Box 60U)
    - Engdahl lecture, 1974 (Box 61)
  - Poetry
    - Consent for publication, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 601)
    - Correspondence (Box 62)
      - General, 1973-1980 (Box 62, Folder 602)
      - Publishers, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 603)
    - "Flowers are Better", 1980 (Box 62, Folder 604)
    - Leaflets, undated (Box 62, Folder 605)
    - Levine, Barry, undated (Box 62, Folder 606)
    - Memorial publications, 1974-1977 (Box 62, Folder 607)
    - Miscellaneous [drafts, correspondence, notes], 1970-1979 (Box 62, Folder 608)
    - "New Poems", 1970, undated (Box 62, Folder 609)
    - "Remembering Kent", 1973 (Box 62, Folder 610 - 611)
    - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny, "Flowers and Bullets", 1970 (Box 62, Folder 612)
- Additional material, 1970-1985; Accession 1990-M-047
  Received from Paul Keane, 1990.
  See also Series II. Paul Keane Papers and Accessions 1982-M-016 and 2006-M-115.
  - Paul Keane papers
    - Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
    - Printed material about the NBC television show "Kent State", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings and printed material, 1980-1985, undated (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Photocopies of address book, Circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Photocopies of diary pages, 1970 October 10-November 22 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Photocopies of the Kent State University Official Bulletin, 1970 May-July (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Daily Kent Stater, 1972 October 11, November 30, 1973 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Additional material, 1989-1990; Accession 1990-M-060
  Received from David C. Calusdian and Jane E. Pierce, 1990.
  - Correspondence about "Kent State-Jackson State: A 20 year retrospective", 1989 December-1990 April (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program, announcement, invitation, and other papers relating to "Kent State-Jackson State: A 20 year retrospective", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles on "Kent State-Jackson State: A 20 year retrospective", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tryout announcement, cast, list, press release, and flyers for "Kent State: A Requiem", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional material, 1979 -1990; Accession 1991-M-004
  Received from Elaine Miller Holstein, 1990.
  - Correspondence and subject files
    - Academic records of Jeff Miller (Box 1)
    - Adams, John P., director of Dept. of Law, Justice and Community Relations, Board of Church and Society, United Methodist Church (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - American Civil Liberties Union of Ohio Foundations, Inc. (Box 1)
    - American Legion (Box 1)
    - "And Still No Honest Apology," Op-Ed article by Elaine Miller Holstein, New York Times, and public responses (Box 1)
    - Boerner, David M. (Box 1)
    - Canfora, Alan and the May 4 Task Force (M4TF) (Box 1)
    - Center for Peaceful Change, KSU (Box 1)